tape4backup.com 2019-03-10

# TAPE 4 BACKUP | T4B

## Collecting Personal Information

We are well aware of your concerns for protecting your personal information, and our staff is committed to securing our client’s privacy. Tape4Backup.com has the Verisign Security Certificates. So feel confident as Verisign industry standard encryption is used to process the orders.  
The purpose of collecting information is to accurately process the order and make the shopping experience of our customers more personalized. We Guarantee that the information is safe and will never be rented, sold or disclosed to third party. Customers can shop with us having peace of mind. Every transaction is safe and your credit card is secure.

## Data Security

We have the industry’s most renowned Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software that  protects your online transactions with  256 bit encoding. Your address, name and credit card is encrypted then safely transferred over the internet. We take robust precautions to secure all personal information for online & offline transactions. Employees with security clearance are only authorized to view full information.   
Security of Tape4backup.com is verified by DSS (Data Security Standard) and PCI.  They perform a number of stringent tests including forensic analysis, PCI audits, PCI scans etc. 

## Monitor Your Personal Information 

  * View their entire personal information. 
  * Edit and delete any information.
  * Express their concerns regarding usage of their personal data.

## Data Sharing 

The orders are shipped through USPS, FEDEX, UPS and many other courier companies. They use the personally identifiable data only for order delivery and not for any other purpose.

## Our website uses cookies 

This feature stores data on your hard disk. The result is quick identification of repeat customers and accelerates the users’ access to Tape4Backup.com enabling us to enhance your shopping experience. With cookies enabled on the site, the users would only need to log in their password once. This smart approach saves times and is not linked to users’ personal data stored on our website.   
Other cookies being used by [Tape4Backup.com](http://www.tape4backup.com/) are:

## Google Analytics and Adwords 

**Analytics**  provides information regarding the activities of the visitors on Tape4Backup.com like visit duration, page views etc. Your privacy is protected as this information is available as digits only. It is not possible to track back to the users.

## Adwords

facilitates us to efficiently utilize the paid search budget. It provides precise information of the web pages that resulted in order placement.
